The radiance of the night shines through my window
but the path to immortality is long.
The Eight Views and Nine-Bend Streams are desolate.
Living beings question the miseries of the world over a jar of wine.
Forget about Nirvana and rebirth,
I will break through the waves with my own flesh and blood.
The heavens are vast, so what if I was born mediocre ?
I stare at the Dao in my moments of madness
as the storm rages just below.
I've been thinking about life and death in my dreams.
I've unsheathed my sword to ask the immortals
why the world is a-changing.
Heaven and earth reveals its poignant truths.
Swallow the Four Seas and the Eight Wastelands,
experience all the vicissitudes of life in an instant.
I will defy the light in the sky
to continue to write a new chapter for all things in the three realms of existence.
Just a thought separates mortal from immortal.
Transform your insignificant body into light.
The hardships of the journey
will temper this young man's heart.
If I become a Renegade Immortal, will I hesitate to fight the heavens ?
Renegade Immortal
Subtitles by Bonobosubs
https://discord.gg/Ceckd4pdVA
Master Teng Nine,
it's time.
Your challenger this time
Teng Yun
Middle stage Nascent Soul
is Teng Yun.
The Ancestor said
that prosperity lies
within the Core Family Members.
Teng Nine
Middle stage Nascent Soul
Teng Family Core Member
The position cannot be inherited.
Anyone in the Teng Family can compete for the spot.
The winner is determined
through a life or death duel.
The spiritual energy of the Spirit Veins...
All the pills and artifacts...
Today, I will become a Core Member
and take Teng Nine's position !
He dares to keep his eyes closed ?
How arrogant !
Young Teng Nine
I admit defeat Brother, I admit defeat !
I have already lost...
Lost ?
But you're not dead yet.
I admit defeat !
I... I've already admitted defeat.
Someone help me !
Delicious.
Teng Nine
The name of Teng Nine
has already been passed 6 times.
Teng Huayuan
Teng Family Ancestor
Peak Late stage Nascent Soul
Every time,
the younger generation gets stronger.
Weaklings
should be discarded.
Teng Nine is still inexperienced.
Out of the 9, he is the Core Family Member
with the weakest cultivation.
He still reached Middle stage Nascent Soul
Given enough time,
each of the 9 Nascent Souls
will have the potential to reach Soul Formation.
Given enough time ?
Your Teng Family
has 100 years.
Lin Yi
Heaven’s Tower Envoy
Early stage Soul Formation
So far,
no one has understood a domain.
It's like sitting in a well, looking at the sky.
A domain is not something understood easily.
without my ancestor's help,
Even I,
would have had trouble forming my Rain Domain.
In 100 years,
if the Teng Family fails to produce a Soul Formation cultivator,
I will take back everything I have given you.
Lord Envoy can rest assured,
the Teng Family
will produce a Soul Formation cultivator.
Remember what you said today.
Li'er,
it should've been you.
With your talent,
you would've reached Soul Formation by now.
Those 9 Nascent Souls feed off the Spirit Veins.
If I destroy those,
they will appear before me.
Are we going to destroy this Wufeng Valley ?
You can leave it to me !
I will kill them !
Master won't even have to move.
In the country of Zhao, Wufeng Valley was the strongest sect.
Wufeng Valley
But now...
Teng Shan
Teng Family Core Disciple
Early stage Core formation
You are so pathetic,
don't you feel ashamed !?
Wu Hongming
Wufeng Valley Disciple
Late stage Core Formation
You're the Senior Brother of Wufeng Valley,
the direct disciple of the Sect Leader.
You fight using Nascent Soul artifacts,
what are you so proud of !?
They fight for the position of Elder,
he's supposed to display his own strength,
not that of his borrowed Nascent Soul artifacts.
What example for the disciples is this ?
Teng Gao
Wufeng Valley Elder
Late stage Core Formation
Every disciple of the Teng Family is given
their own Nascent Soul artifact.
This isn't borrowed strength.
He is using his own weapon
and he respects the Sect's rules.
I'm surprised that even your best disciple
doesn't have a Nascent Soul artifact.
I really don't get it.
Just admit that you are a waste !
I never will !
That's a shame !
Bastard, fight me directly !
Hongming !
Wait.
The Sect Leader hasn't announced the result yet.
Moving now is against the Sect's rules.
Wu Qingfeng
Wufeng Valley Sect Leader
Middle Stage Nascent Soul
Wufeng Valley already lost 5 Elders,
This is problematic...
The Teng Family seized all the positions.
Do you think I don't know what you're doing ?
If you are unsatisfied,
you can discuss this with Teng Nine.
I am sure he is also very worried
about what is going on here.
The winner is
Teng Shan.
He will now
hold the position of Elder.
What's happening !?
The formation is being attacked ?!
Hold on !
Sect Leader !
Someone broke through the first defensive layer.
Don't move !
Calm down !
Keep the formation up !
Wufeng Valley...
It indeed used to be the top sect of Zhao.
The power of this formation
is at the peak of Nascent Soul.
I have heard of the strength of Wufeng Valley's formation.
Seeing it with my own eyes
is extraordinary !
Magnificent !
It will soon be
the best formation of our Teng Family.
This formation is very strong,
it's derived from a restriction.
Since this formation uses sword energy,
I will beat it with sword energy !
10 000 Swords Restriction,
activate !
Come at me !
Break !
What cultivation is he at ?
He beat it in one move ?
Wufeng Valley,
doesn't know how it offended fellow cultivator.
I came here
to kill everyone named Teng.
Whether I become enemy of Wufeng Valley
depends on your attitude.
You !
You destroyed our Spirit Vein of the Tiandao Sect
and you killed Teng Xuan !
Who is Teng Xuan ?
The names of your family
are not worth remembering.
Not worth remembering !?
How dare you !?
Wufeng Valley,
once the top sect of Zhao
Its Sect Leader is bright
and respectable.
But after seeing you today,
Sect Leader Wu,
I see you have become a dog.
What does fellow cultivator mean ?
I'm not sure I understand.
400 years ago,
these mountains were full of spiritual energy
and surrounded by beautiful light.
But now they look miserable and exhausted.
I ask Sect Leader,
is this related to the Teng Family draining the Spirit Veins ?
I said,
I don't understand what fellow cultivator means by that.
Sect Leader,
let's give Teng Gao to him.
This is a great opportunity !
Indeed,
let's rid Wufeng Valley of the Teng Family !
Do you think I don't want to ?
But,
who can beat Teng Nine ?
Interesting... Interesting !
Wufeng Valley and the Teng Family have always been good friends.
Fellow cultivator's cultivation is profound
but if you want to wreck havoc in Wufeng Valley,
you will have to step over our dead bodies !
Who said
that he is going to kill my Teng Family ?
Here he is.
Fellow cultivator Teng Nine,
please don't hurt the disciples of Wufeng Valley.
Nonsense !
Both are Middle stage Nascent Soul
but his pressure is stronger.
So this is a Teng Family Core Member ?
So he was raised using Spirit Veins ?
Master, it's him !
He is the one who killed Teng Shan.
He arrogantly he said he'd kill everyone named Teng in Wufeng Valley !
You overestimate yourself.
My Nascent Soul ghosts
will use their bodies
to block your sword energy.
You
will soon
become one of them.
Break !
Is that all you've got ?
This guy fighting Teng Nine
will win for sure !
Where is he ?
Damn it !
I will capture you and refine you for 1000 years !
Really ?
Then taste this.
Brother, take this.
Delicious !
Look at you.
Brother...
Impossible...
This isn't possible !
Teng Nine came out
and lost !
Master, please spare my life.
Please spare my life !
So, what do we do ?
Wufeng Valley was the top sect of Zhao,
but the Teng Family oppressed us for hundreds of years
to the point of collapse.
But today,
Teng Nine's blood was spilled on our gate.
Wufeng Valley will not let the Teng Family go unpunished.
From now on,
we sever all ties we had with the Teng Family !
Disciples of Wufeng Valley, listen up.
I order you to kill the Teng Family members.
Every single one !
Yes Sect Leader !
Teng Two,
Teng Three,
Teng Four,
lead all cultivators Core Formation and above
and get rid of this murderer immediately !
Those who dare to kill our Teng Family
will be destroyed
with their family
and their souls !
Wang Zhuo
Wang Lin's cousin
Middle stage Nascent Soul
I've had my share of wounds,
now I want to fight back.
Is my destiny a wall of restrictions
that's blocking all my hopes
for life ?
My flesh and blood witnessed the past,
my adversity pushed me to brave the waves.
How do you navigate through the years passing by ?
Nirvana and rebirth are no longer
out of reach.
Immortals
are obsessed with delusions of grandeur.
Renegades
seek to crush the impermanence of the heavens.
Don't tell me that I overestimate myself
and that the path to revenge leads to hell
because I don't see the harm in that.
My new body opens its eyes
and awakens from its dream.
I have overcome many trials
to get this body back.
No matter how many endless dark nights go by,
I can still see.
By sticking to this thought, I will get it done
by my own hands.
Returning to my body opened my eyes,
I need to continue my Immortal journey.
With a flick of a finger,
only my indomitable heart remains.
Life and death trials temper me, I am not afraid of losing my soul.
Even if there are countless tribulations and hardships.
Overcome this fate, smash through the obstacles,
like the descent of a god.